She doesn't seem to care about me like she used to.
لا يبدو أنها تهتم بي كما كانت تفعل سابقاً.
The things she used to do for me, sometimes she forgets,
الأشياء التي كانت تفعلها من أجلي، أحياناً تنسى،
sometimes she doesn't remember to do them.
«أحياناً لا تتذكر القيام بها.»
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
If that's how it's going to be, we should live our own lives.
إذا كان هذا هو الحال، فعلينا أن نعيش حياتنا كما نريد.
What do you mean, live our own lives?
ماذا تقصد، أن نعيش حياتنا الخاصة؟
We should break up.
يجب أن ننفصل.
I want you to know something. When I tell you to go,
أريدك أن تعرف شيئاً. عندما أقول لك اذهب،
I don't really want you to leave.
لا أريدك حقاً أن تغادر.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Hello there, pretty girl.
مرحباً أيتها الفتاة الجميلة.
Do you want some? I can share with you.
هل تريد بعضاً؟ يمكنني أن أشاركك.
Aren't you going to eat it?
ألن تأكله؟
No, I'll eat this one instead.
لا، سآكل هذه بدلاً من ذلك.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- تفضل. - شكراً لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
- Here you go.
- تفضل.
My kid's ugly, right?
طفلي قبيح، أليس كذلك؟
Why would you say ugly? Your baby is so--
لماذا تقولين إنه قبيح؟ طفلكِ جميل جدًا.
Hey! You're not supposed to call babies cute.
مهلاً! ليس من المفترض أن تصف الأطفال بأنهم لطيفون.
They'll get sick. It's an old belief.
سيمرضون. إنه اعتقاد قديم.
Oh, okay.
حسناً، لا بأس.
Fun, can you watch Euro for a second? I need to use the bathroom.
مرح، هل يمكنك مشاهدة مباراة اليورو لثانية؟ أحتاج إلى استخدام الحمام.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Oh, your mitten fell off.
أوه، لقد سقط قفازك.
Oh.
أوه.
Your hands are so tiny. How do I even put this on?
يداك صغيرتان جداً. كيف أرتدي هذا؟
Okay, come here.
حسناً، تعال إلى هنا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
It smells so good.
رائحته جميلة جداً.
This smells good.
هذه رائحة طيبة.
And this smells good too.
ورائحتها جميلة أيضاً.
Go sit down before it gets cold.
اذهب واجلس قبل أن يبرد الجو.
- Go. - Mm.
- انطلق. - مم.
Wow, this is quite a special meal.
يا له من وجبة مميزة!
Does it look good?
هل يبدو جيداً؟
So?
لذا؟
With that face, that smile…
بهذا الوجه، بتلك الابتسامة...
what do you want? A new bag from the latest collection?
ماذا تريدين؟ حقيبة جديدة من أحدث تشكيلة؟
No.
لا.
Shoes?
أحذية؟
Fun,
هزار،
if it's clothes, I'm not letting you buy any more.
إذا كان الأمر يتعلق بالملابس، فلن أسمح لك بشراء المزيد.
You already have too many.
لديك الكثير بالفعل.
- Oon. - Mm.
- نعم. - إلخ.
I want to have a baby.
أريد أن أنجب طفلاً.
But we can talk about it later tonight.
لكن يمكننا التحدث عن ذلك لاحقاً هذه الليلة.
Right now, you should eat,
يجب أن تأكل الآن.
and we both need to get to work.
وكلانا بحاجة إلى البدء بالعمل.
RIGHT TO HAVE CHILDREN FOR LGBTQ COUPLES
حق الأزواج من مجتمع الميم في إنجاب الأطفال
MANY COUNTRIES ALLOW LGBTQ COUPLES
تسمح العديد من الدول بزواج المثليين والمتحولين جنسياً
TO HAVE CHILDREN IN VARIOUS WAYS,
إنجاب الأطفال بطرق متنوعة،
INDIVIDUAL ADOPTION, JOINT ADOPTION, IVF, SURROGACY.
التبني الفردي، التبني المشترك، التلقيح الصناعي، تأجير الأرحام.
THAILAND LEGALIZED SAME-SEX MARRIAGE, GIVING LGBTQ COUPLES MORE FAMILY RIGHTS.
أقرت تايلاند زواج المثليين، مما منح الأزواج من مجتمع الميم المزيد من الحقوق الأسرية.
JOINT ADOPTION, ASSISTED REPRODUCTIVE TECHNOLOGY.
التبني المشترك، تقنيات الإنجاب المساعدة.
IVF PROCESS
عملية التلقيح الصناعي
OVARIAN STIMULATION, EGG RETRIEVAL, SPERM COLLECTION, FERTILIZATION,
تحفيز المبيض، استخراج البويضات، جمع الحيوانات المنوية، الإخصاب،
EMBRYO CULTURE, EMBRYO TRANSFER, PREGNANCY TEST
زراعة الأجنة، نقل الأجنة، اختبار الحمل
IN VITRO FERTILIZATION
التخصيب في المختبر
For the design, I want a modern minimalist style.
بالنسبة للتصميم، أريد أسلوباً عصرياً بسيطاً.
Also, please consider openings
يرجى أيضًا النظر في الوظائف الشاغرة
and natural lighting
والإضاءة الطبيعية
and make sure the systems are easy to maintain.
وتأكد من سهولة صيانة الأنظمة.
Of course. I've prepared several options.
بالتأكيد. لقد أعددت عدة خيارات.
Let's continue the discussion in the meeting room.
لنواصل النقاش في غرفة الاجتماعات.
Sounds good, thank you.
يبدو جيداً، شكراً لك.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Mr. Krit, hello.
مرحباً سيد كريت.
The MD is on the way.
الطبيب في الطريق.
That's fine. I'm free today.
لا بأس. أنا متفرغ اليوم.
The woman who just walked by with Ms. Nam, is she a client?
هل المرأة التي مرت للتو مع السيدة نام هي إحدى زبائنها؟
Oh, no, that's Ms. Pafun.
أوه، لا، إنها الآنسة بافون.
She's the interior designer for the show house.
هي مصممة الديكور الداخلي للمنزل النموذجي.
Do you need anything?
هل تحتاج إلى أي شيء؟
No, I think I just recognized her.
لا، أعتقد أنني تعرفت عليها للتو.
Please wait in the lounge.
يرجى الانتظار في الصالة.
It's okay. I'll wait here. The weather's nice today.
لا بأس. سأنتظر هنا. الجو جميل اليوم.
I'll revise the design and send it over by email for you to review.
سأقوم بتعديل التصميم وإرساله إليك عبر البريد الإلكتروني لمراجعته.
That sounds great. Thank you so much, Ms. Fun.
هذا رائع. شكراً جزيلاً لكِ يا آنسة فن.
- Thank you.
- شكراً لك.
Is there something you need?
هل تحتاج إلى شيء ما؟
Hey, you really don't remember me?
ألا تتذكرني حقاً؟
Do you use this line on girls often?
هل تستخدم هذه العبارة مع الفتيات كثيراً؟
I'm married, by the way.
أنا متزوج، بالمناسبة.
Still as fierce as ever, little sim.
لا تزال شرسة كما كانت دائمًا، يا سيم الصغير.
Wait, Krit?!
انتظر، كريت؟!
You've changed so much I didn't recognize you.
لقد تغيرت كثيراً لدرجة أنني لم أتعرف عليك.
And you're still just as fierce.
وما زلتِ بنفس الشراسة.
When did you get back?
متى عدت؟
Just last week. I'm planning to work here in Thailand now.
الأسبوع الماضي فقط. أخطط الآن للعمل هنا في تايلاند.
What do you do?
ماذا تفعل؟
Construction management consulting.
الاستشارات في إدارة الإنشاءات.
Oh, same field then. I do interior design.
أوه، نفس المجال إذن. أنا أعمل في التصميم الداخلي.
Perfect. Let me get your contact. Let's grab dinner sometime.
ممتاز. سأحصل على رقم هاتفك. لنتناول العشاء معاً في وقت ما.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
One moment.
لحظة من فضلك.
Yes, Peter?
نعم يا بيتر؟
Are you still talking with the client?
هل ما زلت تتحدث مع العميل؟
I just finished.
انتهيت للتو.
Then where are you now? The next client is already waiting.
إذن أين أنت الآن؟ العميل التالي ينتظرك بالفعل.
Got it. I'll head over now.
فهمت. سأذهب الآن.
Krit, I'm running late. We'll talk later, okay?
كريت، أنا متأخر. سنتحدث لاحقاً، حسناً؟
AIOON: DONE
أيون: تم
AIOON: WORKING
أيون: يعمل
Sit down first.
اجلس أولاً.
Fun.
هزار.
From what I've researched,
بحسب ما بحثت فيه،
legally,
قانونياً،
we probably can't do IVF.
ربما لا يمكننا إجراء عملية التلقيح الصناعي.
Surrogacy isn't really an option either.
لا يُعدّ تأجير الأرحام خياراً مطروحاً أيضاً.
The most feasible way is adoption.
الطريقة الأكثر جدوى هي التبني.
Oon, thank you for looking all this up.
أون، شكراً لك على البحث عن كل هذا.
But I already knew we couldn't have a child together.
لكنني كنت أعرف مسبقاً أننا لا نستطيع إنجاب طفل معاً.
Are you upset?
هل أنت منزعج؟
Not at all. I made my choice.
لا على الإطلاق. لقد اتخذت قراري.
Since the day I decided to be with you,
منذ اليوم الذي قررت فيه أن أكون معك،
I understood all of this.
لقد فهمت كل هذا.
Oh? Then why did you suddenly say you wanted a baby?
أوه؟ إذن لماذا قلتِ فجأةً إنكِ تريدين طفلاً؟
Oh, because we promised to talk about everything.
أوه، لأننا وعدنا بالتحدث عن كل شيء.
Well, I just met Peter and Aor's baby.
حسناً، لقد قابلت للتو طفل بيتر وأور.
She's so adorable. You know, the moment she held my finger,
إنها رائعة للغاية. أتعرف، في اللحظة التي أمسكت فيها بإصبعي،
it felt like the whole world stopped.
شعرت وكأن العالم كله توقف.
And my heart felt a kind of warmth I've never felt before.
وشعر قلبي بنوع من الدفء لم أشعر به من قبل.
Then when we're ready, let's adopt a child.
ثم عندما نكون مستعدين، فلنتبنى طفلاً.
You should've told me everything from the start.
كان عليك أن تخبرني بكل شيء منذ البداية.
Do you know
هل تعلم
I couldn't even focus on work
لم أستطع حتى التركيز على العمل
because I was researching all this?
لأنني كنت أبحث في كل هذا؟
Poor you.
يا لك من مسكين.
Not happening. I have work early tomorrow.
لن يحدث ذلك. لدي عمل مبكر غداً.
I had high hopes.
كانت لدي آمال كبيرة.
- Fun. - Hmm?
- ممتع. - همم؟
Hurry up, or you're sleeping outside tonight.
أسرع، وإلا ستنام في العراء الليلة.
Oh, no compensation, and I still have to sleep outside?
أوه، لا يوجد تعويض، وما زلت مضطراً للنوم في العراء؟
Are you coming or not?
هل ستأتي أم لا؟
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
Oon-Oon.
أون أون.
Yes.
نعم.
- Aioon. - Yeah, yeah, I know.
- أيون. - أجل، أجل، أعرف.
Aioon.
أنا سوف.
Mr. Kritsana,
السيد كريتسانا،
this is Ms. Wirinya, our designer.
هذه السيدة ويرينيا، مصممتنا.
And that's Mr. Thanwa, the architect for this project.
وهذا هو السيد ثانوا، المهندس المعماري لهذا المشروع.
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
Ms. Aioon.
السيدة أيون.
I'm a friend of Pafun.
أنا صديق لبافون.
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
Let's sit down.
هيا نجلس.
What kind of complex design are you looking for?
ما نوع التصميم المعقد الذي تبحث عنه؟
Do you have any guidelines in mind?
هل لديك أي توجيهات في ذهنك؟
The client wants a single-story layout.
يرغب العميل في تصميم من طابق واحد.
Include a supermarket, restaurants
يشمل ذلك سوبر ماركت ومطاعم
and a cafe, everything in one place.
ومقهى، كل شيء في مكان واحد.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Anything else?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر؟
Just make it look good.
اجعله يبدو جيداً فحسب.
You can trust Mr. Thanwa on that.
يمكنك الوثوق بالسيد ثانوا في هذا الأمر.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I just ran into Fun a few days ago.
لقد التقيت بـ "فن" قبل بضعة أيام فقط.
Oh, really?
أوه حقًا؟
Fun was my first love, you know.
المرح كان حبي الأول، كما تعلم.
It smells so good.
رائحته جميلة جداً.
Let's eat.
هيا نأكل.
I'm starving.
أنا جائع.
Oh, today, I met your friend, Kritsana.
أوه، اليوم قابلت صديقتك، كريتسانا.
Oh, Krit. Yeah, I just ran into him too. I forgot to tell you.
أوه، كريت. أجل، لقد قابلته للتو أيضاً. نسيت أن أخبرك.
He's Aunt Sa-Ngad's son.
إنه ابن العمة سا-نغاد.
Aunt Sa-Ngad?
العمة سا-نغاد؟
Aunt Sa-Ngad… ah, your mom's neighbor.
العمة سا-نغاد... آه، جارة والدتك.
He's the client for my new project.
هو العميل لمشروعي الجديد.
Oh, really? Thanks.
أوه، حقاً؟ شكراً.
Krit and I used to play together almost every day when we were kids.
اعتدت أنا وكريت أن نلعب معًا كل يوم تقريبًا عندما كنا أطفالًا.
But after he went abroad in high school,
لكن بعد أن سافر إلى الخارج في المرحلة الثانوية،
we lost touch.
انقطعت علاقتنا.
Oon, try this, tom kha gai.
أون، جرب هذا، توم خا غاي.
Opal said it's really good.
قالت أوبال إنه جيد حقاً.
I'll get some for you.
سأحضر لك بعضاً منها.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
It's really good.
إنه جيد حقاً.
Here.
هنا.
- Thank you. - Eat more.
- شكراً لك. - تناول المزيد من الطعام.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
It's me, Krit.
أنا كريت.
Oh, Krit. What's up?
أوه، كريت. ما الأمر؟
I have a client to introduce. Are you taking new jobs?
لدي عميل أريد تعريفه بك. هل تقبل وظائف جديدة؟
Yes, I am. You can send the details via email.
نعم، أنا كذلك. يمكنك إرسال التفاصيل عبر البريد الإلكتروني.
It's quite detailed. I'd be better if I explain it to you. It's a condo unit.
إنها مفصلة للغاية. سيكون من الأفضل لو شرحتها لك. إنها وحدة سكنية.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then I'll prepare a quotation for you.
ثم سأقوم بإعداد عرض سعر لك.
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
The client's my friend.
العميل صديقي.
I'd rather set up a meeting first, then you can quote later.
أفضّل تحديد موعد للاجتماع أولاً، ثم يمكنك تقديم عرض سعر لاحقاً.
Okay. One second, Krit.
حسناً. لحظة من فضلك يا كريت.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Oh?
أوه؟
SPEAKER
المتحدث
Yes, Krit.
نعم يا كريت.
My friend is rather picky
صديقي صعب الإرضاء نوعاً ما
but not that much.
لكن ليس بهذا القدر.
And
و
what style does your friend prefer? Minimal,
ما هو النمط الذي يفضله صديقك؟ بسيط،
loft, modern,
دور علوي، حديث،
or classic?
أو كلاسيكي؟
Probably modern.
ربما حديث.
And he wants the space to feel more open.
ويريد أن يشعر المرء بأن المكان أكثر اتساعاً.
Got it. I'll send some references.
فهمت. سأرسل بعض المراجع.
Actually,
في الواقع،
let's just have a video call.
لنقم بمكالمة فيديو.
Easier than going back and forth.
أسهل من الذهاب والإياب.
Okay.
تمام.
How could you see anything with that?
كيف يمكنك أن ترى أي شيء من خلال ذلك؟
Is this okay?
هل هذا مناسب؟
Yeah, this looks good.
نعم، هذا يبدو جيداً.
Okay. If you like this, I'll design the furniture
حسنًا. إذا أعجبك هذا، فسأصمم الأثاث.
and match the color palette.
ومطابقة لوحة الألوان.
Sounds good.
يبدو جيداً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Oh, and how's Aunt Anong?
أوه، وكيف حال العمة أنونغ؟
When are you visiting home again?
متى ستزور بلدك مرة أخرى؟
Well, my mom's doing well. I just visited recently.
حسناً، والدتي بخير. لقد زرتها مؤخراً.
Would you like me to design the entire space, bedroom,
هل ترغبين أن أصمم لكِ المساحة بأكملها، غرفة النوم؟
kitchen, everything?
المطبخ، كل شيء؟
Yeah, probably everything.
أجل، ربما كل شيء.
By the way, when are you free?
بالمناسبة، متى تكون متفرغاً؟
I've got a lot to update you on.
لدي الكثير لأطلعك عليه.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Yes, Krit?
نعم يا كريت؟
Just a sec, okay?
لحظة من فضلك، حسناً؟
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
Yes?
نعم؟
Fun.
مرح.
You might meet the client I mentioned today.
قد تقابل العميل الذي ذكرته اليوم.
I'll confirm the time and place later.
I'll confirm the time and place later.
Can you make it?
Can you make it?
I think so.
I think so.
Then please prepare more references for me.
Then please prepare more references for me.
Krit… again?
Krit… again?
Everyone, please revise everything based on my briefing.
Everyone, please revise everything based on my briefing.
- Yes.
- Yes.
Please revise it.
Please revise it.
- Sure.
- Sure.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
PAFUN
PAFUN
Yes, Fun?
Yes, Fun?
Oon-oon, can you talk?
Oon-oon, can you talk?
I can.
I can.
I just wanted to let you know
I just wanted to let you know
I have a meeting tonight with the client Krit set up.
I have a meeting tonight with the client Krit set up.
I might be home late.
I might be home late.
I just wanted to tell you to eat something before going home.
I just wanted to tell you to eat something before going home.
Do you want me to come with you?
Do you want me to come with you?
It's okay. I'll keep it quick and head back.
It's okay. I'll keep it quick and head back.
Okay.
تمام.
Krit, where's the client?
Krit, where's the client?
The client?
The client?
Your friend, the client you mentioned. Where is he?
Your friend, the client you mentioned. Where is he?
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
He said I could handle it. He trusts me.
He said I could handle it. He trusts me.
Here's the layout,
Here's the layout,
98 square meters.
98 square meters.
- Two bedrooms, two bathrooms. - Okay.
- Two bedrooms, two bathrooms. - Okay.
- I'll send it to you. - Thank you.
- I'll send it to you. - Thank you.
Here.
هنا.
He wants the entrance area to feel open and airy.
He wants the entrance area to feel open and airy.
The kitchen will be next to the balcony.
The kitchen will be next to the balcony.
Got it.
Got it.
But first, should we order something to eat?
But first, should we order something to eat?
What would you like?
What would you like?
Anything is fine. You can choose.
Anything is fine. You can choose.
This place is famous for many dishes.
This place is famous for many dishes.
- Excuse me. - Yes, sir.
- Excuse me. - Yes, sir.
I'll have the sour curry sea bass set.
I'll have the sour curry sea bass set.
- Yes. - Hey.
- Yes. - Hey.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Come on. Their shrimp pesto spaghetti
Come on. Their shrimp pesto spaghetti
is so famous. I spent all day finding this place.
is so famous. I spent all day finding this place.
I mean, for my friend.
I mean, for my friend.
Then you go ahead and order. I can eat anything.
Then you go ahead and order. I can eat anything.
Okay.
تمام.
‪Excuse me.
‪Excuse me.
Shrimp pesto spaghetti,
Shrimp pesto spaghetti,
seafood spaghetti,
seafood spaghetti,
Caesar salad,
Caesar salad,
creamy corn salad.
creamy corn salad.
Oh, are you already full? You barely ate.
Oh, are you already full? You barely ate.
Yes, I don't usually eat much for dinner. Please go ahead.
Yes, I don't usually eat much for dinner. Please go ahead.
What about dessert? Their cake is really good.
What about dessert? Their cake is really good.
No, thank you.
No, thank you.
Yes, Oon?
Yes, Oon?
Fun, are you still working?
Fun, are you still working?
Yes, but I'm almost done.
Yes, but I'm almost done.
Do you still have chocolate lava cake?
Do you still have chocolate lava cake?
Two, please.
Two, please.
Fun, I already ordered your favorite chocolate cake for you.
Fun, I already ordered your favorite chocolate cake for you.
Sorry, you're on the phone.
Sorry, you're on the phone.
Our chocolate lava cake is very popular among couples.
Our chocolate lava cake is very popular among couples.
Thank you.
Thank you.
I've gotta go, Oon.
I've gotta go, Oon.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
So,
So,
next to the smaller bedroom, there's a storage room.
next to the smaller bedroom, there's a storage room.
My friend is wondering if he should knock down the wall to expand the space.
My friend is wondering if he should knock down the wall to expand the space.
That could work. It would make the room feel bigger.
That could work. It would make the room feel bigger.
Is he strict about feng shui?
Is he strict about feng shui?
I don't think so.
I don't think so.
He believes
He believes
that as long as you stay ahead of your competitors, you win.
that as long as you stay ahead of your competitors, you win.
No need to believe in things like that.
No need to believe in things like that.
I see.
أرى.
Please pack these to go. And the bill as well.
يرجى تجهيز هذه الأشياء لتأخذوها معكم. وكذلك الفاتورة.
Yes.
نعم.
Krit, you can take the cakes home.
كريت، يمكنكِ أخذ الكعك إلى المنزل.
I don't like chocolate cake.
أنا لا أحب كعكة الشوكولاتة.
I'll pay for this meal. I can reimburse it as a client expense.
سأدفع ثمن هذه الوجبة. يمكنني تعويضها كنفقة خاصة بالعميل.
I'll take care of it.
سأتولى الأمر.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Trust me. It's a small thing. Don't make it a big deal.
صدقني، إنه أمر بسيط. لا تجعله مشكلة كبيرة.
Come on. Let me help carry it.
هيا، دعني أساعدك في حمله.
It's okay. I can carry it myself.
لا بأس. أستطيع حمله بنفسي.
After this, are you heading somewhere?
بعد ذلك، هل ستتجه إلى مكان ما؟
Wanna walk around the avenue next door with me?
هل ترغب في التجول معي في الشارع المجاور؟
I've been there before. There's not much there.
لقد زرت هذا المكان من قبل. لا يوجد فيه الكثير.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Where were you going? Be careful.
إلى أين كنت ذاهباً؟ كن حذراً.
Krit, I'm okay. It's okay.
كريت، أنا بخير. لا بأس.
Krit.
حرب.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'm so tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
Well, you were working late.
حسناً، لقد كنت تعمل لوقت متأخر.
If it were just work, I wouldn't be this tired.
لو كان الأمر مجرد عمل، لما كنت متعباً إلى هذا الحد.
Did he make you uncomfortable?
هل جعلك تشعر بعدم الارتياح؟
If so, just turn the job down. You don't have to do it.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فما عليك سوى رفض الوظيفة. لست مضطراً للقيام بذلك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I already accepted it for the company. I need to finish it.
لقد قبلتُ ذلك بالفعل للشركة. عليّ إنجازه.
I can handle it.
أستطيع التعامل مع الأمر.
Fun, I think that Krit guy is strange.
مرح، أعتقد أن ذلك الرجل كريت غريب الأطوار.
It feels like he's trying to make us fight.
يبدو الأمر وكأنه يحاول أن يجعلنا نتقاتل.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I don't feel anything for him.
لا أشعر تجاهه بأي شيء.
He's just a childhood friend.
إنه مجرد صديق طفولة.
I'll never feel anything for him.
لن أشعر تجاهه بأي شيء على الإطلاق.
Never.
أبداً.
Because I love someone beautiful.
لأنني أحب شخصاً جميلاً.
Especially the beautiful person right in front of me,
وخاصة الشخص الجميل الذي يقف أمامي مباشرة،
the one I love the most.
الشخص الذي أحبه أكثر من غيره.
You started it and didn't finish it.
لقد بدأت الأمر ولم تُنهِه.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Fun.
هزار.
Are you okay? Why do you look so pale?
هل أنت بخير؟ لماذا تبدو شاحباً جداً؟
My stomach hurts.
معدتي تؤلمني.
Are you getting your period?
هل بدأت دورتك الشهرية؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm running late. I'll get up and make you breakfast first.
أنا متأخر. سأستيقظ وأحضر لك الفطور أولاً.
No, don't. Just lie down.
لا، لا تفعل. فقط استلقِ.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Don't get up. Just rest.
لا تنهض. فقط استرح.
It's okay. Just rest.
لا بأس. فقط استرح.
Fun.
هزار.
I made porridge,
لقد صنعت العصيدة،
and I brought you painkillers and a hot water bag.
وأحضرت لك مسكنات للألم وقربة ماء ساخن.
Can you get up and eat?
هل يمكنك النهوض وتناول الطعام؟
I don't feel like eating. Can I sleep a bit more?
لا أشعر برغبة في تناول الطعام. هل يمكنني النوم قليلاً؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
But when you wake up, make sure you eat and take your medicine, okay?
لكن عندما تستيقظ، تأكد من تناول الطعام وتناول دوائك، حسناً؟
Okay.
تمام.
Here, use the hot water bag first.
استخدم قربة الماء الساخن أولاً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'll head to work now.
سأذهب إلى العمل الآن.
But if you need anything, call me anytime.
لكن إذا احتجت إلى أي شيء، فاتصل بي في أي وقت.
Okay.
تمام.
Hey, buddy.
مرحباً يا صديقي.
It's noon. Let's go eat.
حان وقت الظهيرة. هيا بنا نأكل.
Okay, give me a sec.
حسناً، انتظرني لحظة.
Fifa, perfect timing. Help me with this.
فيفا، توقيت مثالي. ساعدني في هذا.
Is this one good?
هل هذا جيد؟
Don't forget to list this out.
لا تنسَ إدراج هذا في القائمة.
OON-OON
أون أون
Yes, Oon?
نعم، أون؟
You're still asleep?
هل ما زلت نائماً؟
It's almost noon. Have you eaten and taken your medicine?
اقتربت الساعة من الثانية عشرة ظهراً. هل تناولت طعامك وأدويتك؟
I don't want to eat. My stomach hurts.
لا أريد أن آكل. معدتي تؤلمني.
Just eat a little, so you can take your medicine.
تناول القليل من الطعام فقط، حتى تتمكن من تناول دوائك.
I said my stomach hurts. That's it.
قلت إن معدتي تؤلمني. هذا كل شيء.
If you don't take your meds, how is it supposed to stop hurting?
إذا لم تتناول أدويتك، فكيف من المفترض أن يتوقف الألم؟
Oon?
هل أنا كذلك؟
How did you get here?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
The sofa.
الأريكة.
I took the day off.
أخذت إجازة اليوم.
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
Yeah,
نعم،
two bites of porridge.
لقمتين من العصيدة.
Did you take your medicine?
هل تناولت دوائك؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
Are you hungry?
هل أنت جائع؟
No.
لا.
- I don't feel like eating. - Okay.
- لا أشعر برغبة في تناول الطعام. - حسناً.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
What's that smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
There's corn som tam, bamboo shoot soup,
يوجد حساء سوم تام بالذرة، وحساء براعم الخيزران،
grilled pork neck and mushroom soup.
حساء رقبة الخنزير المشوية مع الفطر.
I told you I don't want to eat.
قلت لك إني لا أريد أن آكل.
Just a little, okay? I wasn't sure what you'd feel like eating,
قليل فقط، حسناً؟ لم أكن متأكداً مما ترغب بتناوله.
so I got both versions, with and without fermented fish sauce.
لذا حصلت على كلا النسختين، مع صلصة السمك المخمرة وبدونها.
Just try a bit, okay?
جرب قليلاً، حسناً؟
- Here. - Thank you.
- تفضل. - شكراً لك.
This one doesn't have fermented fish sauce.
هذا النوع لا يحتوي على صلصة سمك مخمرة.
Want to try the one that does?
هل ترغب بتجربة المنتج الذي يفعل ذلك؟
Oon, wake up.
أون، استيقظي.
Oon, Oon.
نعم، نعم.
Are you sick?
هل أنت مريض؟
My stomach hurts. My period came last night.
معدتي تؤلمني. لقد أتتني الدورة الشهرية الليلة الماضية.
Oh, right,
أوه، صحيح.
yours comes after mine.
يأتي دورك بعد دوري.
Good thing today's Saturday.
لحسن الحظ أن اليوم هو السبت.
Are you feeling better now?
هل تشعر بتحسن الآن؟
Yeah, I'm feeling better.
نعم، أشعر بتحسن.
Then you rest. I'll go prepare food for you.
ثم استرح. سأذهب لأحضر لك الطعام.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Fun, my stomach hurts.
مرح، معدتي تؤلمني.
Okay, I won't tease you anymore.
حسناً، لن أضايقك بعد الآن.
That's all?
هذا كل شيء؟
Yes. That's all.
نعم. هذا كل شيء.
What about bamboo shoot soup?
ماذا عن حساء براعم الخيزران؟
I want something spicy.
أريد شيئاً حاراً.
Who eats fermented food during their period?
من يتناول الأطعمة المخمرة أثناء فترة الحيض؟
You ate it yesterday.
لقد أكلته بالأمس.
Well, you bought it, so I had to eat it.
حسناً، أنت من اشتريته، لذا كان عليّ أن آكله.
Otherwise, it would've gone to waste.
وإلا، لكانت قد ذهبت سدى.
Look, everything here is good for you.
انظر، كل شيء هنا مفيد لك.
Porridge for energy,
عصيدة للحصول على الطاقة،
ginger tea for inflammation, painkillers for pain relief.
شاي الزنجبيل لعلاج الالتهابات، ومسكنات الألم لتخفيف الألم.
And if that's not enough, there's the hot water bag.
وإذا لم يكن ذلك كافياً، فهناك قربة الماء الساخن.
Come on, hurry up and eat, so you can take your medicine.
هيا، أسرع وتناول الطعام، حتى تتمكن من أخذ دوائك.
Double standards.
معايير مزدوجة.
If you want something spicy, I'll prepare it for your next meal.
إذا كنت ترغب في شيء حار، فسأقوم بتحضيره لك في وجبتك القادمة.
But no bamboo shoot soup.
لكن لا يوجد حساء براعم الخيزران.
- Or are you not eating? - I'll eat.
- أم أنك لا تأكل؟ - سآكل.
No bamboo shoot soup.
لا يوجد حساء براعم الخيزران.
Oon, the complex site got approved already.
أوون، تمت الموافقة على موقع المجمع بالفعل.
That was fast, start to finish.
كان ذلك سريعاً، من البداية إلى النهاية.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Hey, I heard this client specifically requested you.
مرحباً، سمعت أن هذا العميل طلب خدماتك تحديداً.
I've never even met them.
لم أقابلهم قط.
What do you mean? It's your girlfriend's friend.
ماذا تقصد؟ إنها صديقة حبيبتك.
Oh, and in two days, we have to send everything to the consultant.
أوه، وفي غضون يومين، علينا إرسال كل شيء إلى المستشار.
Please gather all the documents and have a messenger deliver them to their office.
يرجى جمع جميع المستندات وإرسال مندوب لتسليمها إلى مكتبهم.
Nu, Nat got into an accident yesterday. He's in the hospital.
نو، نات تعرض لحادث أمس. إنه في المستشفى.
We'll probably need an external messenger.
ربما سنحتاج إلى وسيط خارجي.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
It's okay, I'll deliver them myself.
لا بأس، سأقوم بتوصيلها بنفسي.
Sounds good.
ًيبدو جيدا.
Come in.
ادخل.
Ms. Aioon.
السيدة أيون.
Please come in.
تفضل بالدخول.
- Hello.
- مرحباً.
These are the documents.
هذه هي الوثائق.
Please have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
Honestly, you could've just sent these with a messenger.
بصراحة، كان بإمكانك إرسالها عبر تطبيق مراسلة.
I happened to be nearby,
لقد كنتُ في مكان قريب بالصدفة،
so I thought I'd drop them off myself, just in case anything needed fixing.
لذلك فكرت في أن أوصلها بنفسي، تحسباً لأي شيء يحتاج إلى إصلاح.
There shouldn't be any issues. I've reviewed everything.
لا ينبغي أن تكون هناك أي مشاكل. لقد راجعت كل شيء.
Your work is very thorough. It's impressive.
عملك دقيق للغاية. إنه مثير للإعجاب.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Come in.
ادخل.
Have you ever thought about taking on projects independently?
هل فكرت يوماً في تولي مشاريع بشكل مستقل؟
I have a lot of clients.
لدي الكثير من العملاء.
If you join my team, I guarantee
إذا انضممت إلى فريقي، فأنا أضمن لك ذلك.
you'll earn a lot.
ستربح الكثير.
Thank you for the offer,
شكراً على العرض.
but I don't think I'm capable enough to work with you, Mr. Kritsana.
لكنني لا أعتقد أنني أمتلك القدرة الكافية للعمل معك يا سيد كريتسانا.
- Excuse me. - Come in.
- معذرةً. - تفضل بالدخول.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
There’s a budget document that urgently needs your signature.
هناك وثيقة ميزانية تحتاج إلى توقيعك بشكل عاجل.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
- Here. Thanks. - Yes, sir.
- تفضل. شكراً. - نعم سيدي.
I'll head out now, so you can continue your work.
سأغادر الآن، حتى تتمكن من مواصلة عملك.
It's fine, we can keep talking.
لا بأس، يمكننا الاستمرار في الحديث.
If there's anything else, please let me know.
إذا كان هناك أي شيء آخر، فأرجو إبلاغي.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
If you're ever interested in my offer, feel free to contact me anytime.
إذا كنت مهتمًا بعرضي، فلا تتردد في الاتصال بي في أي وقت.
I'm just offering you a good option,
أنا فقط أقدم لك خياراً جيداً،
a life where you don't have to struggle.
حياة لا تضطر فيها إلى الكفاح.
A house, a car, anything you want, I can give it to you.
بيت، سيارة، أي شيء تريده، يمكنني أن أعطيك إياه.
You don't have to leave Aioon,
لست مضطراً لمغادرة أيون،
but when I call, you come.
لكن عندما أنادي، تأتي.
Oon, what's wrong?
أون، ما الخطب؟
I can't build a future for you anymore.
لم يعد بإمكاني بناء مستقبل لك.
I've been suspended from work.
تم إيقافي عن العمل.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon
ترجمة الترجمة بواسطة: Panuwat Baikeawon